The real inspiration came from Buju Banton,
“Sensimilla Persecution.”
[Duh da da duh da da duh]
He switched the flow up, like he was just
ripping it and then he switched the flow up
and the beat was cutting out.
That’s why the beat cuts out when you hear,
“Ultimate, ultimate, you are the opposite,
stop this shit, chop your esophagus, esophagus.”
Like if somebody trying you and we’re part
of the same click like I have to ride for
you regardless.
And we wet anybody up, you know, like a canteen.
You know what a canteen is.
It contains water so it’s pretty much, I
ride for you.
You ride for me.
Nah I mean, Elimidate is a show, pretty much,
where they go on dates where if they fuck
with them they stay with them if don’t they
eliminate them.
So when I was like “eliminate like Elimidate”
you just X em out.
Cause you watch Dragon Ball Z like whenever
they get really hurt, they’re like, “Yo,
Goku, you have the senzu beans?”
And he’s like “Yeah, I got the senzu beans.”
And they just pop one and then they’re back
to normal all rejuvenated.
Elect me.
Like, I believe in myself.
I should be the goddamn president.
You feel me?
Like, I get change done.
Who’s Obama?
Denzel Obama.
Yes I’m very narcissistic.
People call me ugly but I don’t give a fuck.
I’m handsome
as shit.
I look at myself in
the mirror I’m like damn who that nigga is?
When there was a lot of controversy around
Kony at that time you know everybody was talking
about Kony, like everybody wanted to be Kony
like, even people was like, “Yeah my name
is Asap Kony” like, you know, like on Twitter
and stuff like that and I just brought it
back up.
Yeah I’m from South Florida, you know, I
was born and raised there, Miami Carol City.
And, flow like a foreigner, you know we get
a lot of foreigners because you know people
come off the boat like from Cuba, any type
of island ‘cause most of it’s country
but we’re all islanders at some degree like
my manager is Jamaican, my other manager is
Colombian, I’m Bohemian.
You remember them books, the animorphs?
Everybody be like, “I’m a beast” but
like you used to look at the show animorph,
and it was a book, you know they’ll actually
turn into the beast, they’ll actually turn
into the animal so, I wanted to paint that
picture of me turning into a beast.
Lord Infamous was my favorite rapper at that
time.
Him and Andre 3000.
Those are the only two I really looked up
to at that time.
One was dark and one was light but when it
came down to it both of their flows were great.
I got into Lord Infamous because the shit
he was talking about was just dark as fuck.